{
    "id": "de6567b0e8c3431881d9b4fe893ef07e",
    "title": "Although, though, despite and in spite of",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2ffcb28c972e4a6a9b3a74a0d71eb821",
            "title": "Though, Although, Despite, In Spite Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She went out …………………. it was raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "in spite of",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The trains were late ………………… the rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "because of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I managed to arrive on time …………………. the train was late by an hour.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "despite",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoyed the film …………………. having a headache.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "in spite of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She bought the car ………………… the fact that it was expensive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "because",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dress was good …………….. expensive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "however",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "John was absent. ……………….., everybody else was present.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "However",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. John was absent, everybody else was present.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We managed to do it ……………… we didn’t receive any assistance from them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "however",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We managed to do it ………………….. the fact that we didn’t receive any assistance from them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}